{
    "questions": [
        {
            "answer": "Structured yet flexible",
            "options": [
                "Structured yet flexible",
                "Rigid",
                "Chaotic",
                "Arrogant"
            ],
            "question": "ABA is best when..."
        },
        {
            "answer": "Prediction",
            "options": [
                "Notion",
                "Action",
                "Prediction",
                "Premonition"
            ],
            "question": "What is one purpose of science?"
        },
        {
            "answer": [
                "Experimental analysis of behavior",
                "Applied behavior analysis"
            ],
            "options": [
                "Astrology",
                "Experimental analysis of behavior",
                "Applied behavior analysis",
                "Experiential behavior therapy"
            ],
            "question": "Which 2 of the following are branches of Behavior Analysis?"
        },
        {
            "answer": [
                "Effective",
                "Conceptually systematic"
            ],
            "options": [
                "Effective",
                "Conceptually systematic",
                "Reinforcement",
                "Operant"
            ],
            "question": "Which 2 of the following are Dimensions of ABA as described in the seminal paper by Baer et al (1968)?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Behavior selected & maintained by consequences",
            "options": [
                "Behavior",
                "Behavior determined by antecedents",
                "Behavior selected & maintained by consequences",
                "Everything a person doesâ€¦"
            ],
            "question": "Operant behavior refers to..."
        },
        {
            "answer": "Reinforcing",
            "options": [
                "Conceptually systematic",
                "Generality",
                "Technological",
                "Reinforcing"
            ],
            "question": "Which is NOT a dimension of ABA (Baer et al 1968)?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "One way to analyze behavior (what happened before, what behavior we see & what happens after)",
            "options": [
                "One way to analyze behavior (what happened before, what behavior we see & what happens after)",
                "The function of behavior",
                "Is contingency shaped",
                "Is what it is"
            ],
            "question": "The 'Three-Term-Contingency' is:"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Evidence-Based",
            "options": [
                "Evidence-Based",
                "Faith-Based",
                "Humor-Based",
                "Illusion-Based"
            ],
            "question": "Science is..."
        },
        {
            "answer": [
                "Consistent",
                "Intensive"
            ],
            "options": [
                "Consistent",
                "Intensive",
                "Attitude",
                "Quality"
            ],
            "question": "Three factors that determine successful ABA interventions include being"
        },
        {
            "answer": "False",
            "options": [
                "True",
                "False",
                "Maybe",
                "Not apply"
            ],
            "question": "True or false: ABA is used only with children with Autism?"
        },
        {
            "answer": "Applied behavior analysis",
            "options": [
                "Applying behavioral analysis",
                "Analyzing behavior assessment",
                "All beware alerts!",
                "Applied behavior analysis"
            ],
            "question": "What does ABA stand for?"
        }
    ],
    "questionType": "First QUIZZ_ 7 Dimensions of Applied Behavior Analysis (ABA)",
  "questionID" : "1"
}